wishlist.com 2013-06-06

# The WishList.com Privacy Policy

WishList.com is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Because we gather certain types of information about the users of our site, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. The intent of this document is to outline and answer the following questions:

1\. What information this site gathers/tracks about you

2\. What this site does with the information it gathers/tracks

3\. With whom this site shares the information it gathers/tracks

4\. Children's Guidelines

5\. Security

6\. This site's opt-out policy

7\. This site's policy on correcting and updating personally identifiable information

8\. This site's policy on deleting or deactivating your name from its database

1\. WishList gathers user information in the following processes:

Registration  
During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address. Optionally, we ask for a mailing address to assure the proper delivery of gifts. We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

User Profile  
WishList users have the option of filling out a detailed user profile that allows their friends to discover important purchasing information such as clothing sizes, favorite colors, etc. The user decides whether to fill this information in and who has access to it.

Cookies  
The WishList.com website uses cookies to maintain a user's identity between sessions so that the site can be personalized based on user preferences or a user's history. Cookies are little bits of information that sit on your computer and allow us to remember you each time you visit.

Log Files We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

2\. Use of the Information

Registration  
As stated above, we use customer contact information to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Log Files  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Special Offers  
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

Aggregate Demographics  
This site will aggregate demographic information based on user activity. This data is purely informational and is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

3\. Sharing of Information

WishList provides gift registry services to retailers and other partner sites in order to enhance the quality of our service to you. When these retailers and partner sites refer new customers to WishList, we take information necessary to establish a customer account (username, password, and email address). We share this information only with the referring site, and only if the partner site adopts and adheres to our strict privacy guidelines. Additionally, retailers with products registered by you are given information pertaining only to these products. This data is purely informational and is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We share aggregate information about our users with our business partners and other third parties. This information shows user activity as a whole rather than on an individual basis and cannot be used to individually identify you. We use aggregated information we collect about users to continue to improve our service for you.

This site contains links to other sites. www.wishlist.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

4\. Children's Guidelines

The safety of children is of extreme importance to us. In regards to our practices concerning minors, WishList.com will:

a. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent

b. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent

c. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information without prior parental consent

d. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent

e. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

5\. Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to service@wishlist.com

6\. Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

a. Users may send an email to service@wishlist.com

b. In every e-mail we send, we provide instructions on how to opt out of future mailings.

c. Users may opt out of our e-mail list in the "My Wish List" section of our website

7\. Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:

a. Users may edit or delete their personal information at any time via their "My Wish List" homepage.

b. Users may send an email to service@wishlist.com

8\. Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact

WishList.com, Inc.  
46-E Peninsula Center  
Suite 385  
Rolling Hills Estates, CA 90274  
Tel: 888-310-4504  
legal@wishlist.com
